Guys! Guys! I've got great news. Guess what.
位！各位！ 我有個好消息，猜猜看
- Monica's pregnant! - Really?
-摩妮卡懷孕了！ -真的嗎？
Let's get past the moment.
當我沒說過
- What's your news? - Thank you.
-是什麼好消息呢？ -謝謝
I got a job in advertising.
我找到一個廣告工作了
Honey, that's incredible!
親愛的，這真是太棒了！
Gosh, what's the pay like?
天啊，薪水怎樣呢？
Oh, come on, people.
喔，你們，別這樣
If I don't know who makes the most..
如果我不知道誰賺最多…
how do I know who I like the most? Hi, Joey.
我怎麼知道要最喜歡誰呢？ 嗨，喬伊
It pays nothing. It's an internship.
沒有薪水，是實習的工作
We have interns at Days of Our Lives.
《我們的日子》也有實習生
Right. So it'll be the same, except less sex with you.
沒錯，所以是一樣的東西 不同的只是不用常跟你上床
What do you think they'll have you do there?
你覺得你去那裡要做什麼呢？
It's a training program, but they hire the people they like.
這只是個訓練課程 但是之後他們會聘請他們喜歡的人
- That's great! - There's gonna be some grunt work..
-太棒了！ -一定會有些無聊乏味的工作讓人討厭
which will stink. A grown man getting people coffee is humiliating.
一個大男人幫大家端咖啡真是羞辱
Humiliating and noble.
羞辱，卻高貴
Thank you.
謝謝你
You know, if I didn't already have a job..
如果我不是早有工作了
I would've been good in advertising.
我應該會在廣告業做得很好的
Ross, you did not come up with: "Got Milk?"
羅斯，「今天喝牛奶了嗎？」 不是你想出來的
Yes, I did! I did!
是的，是我想的！是我！
I should've written it down.
我應該要把它先寫下來的
The One With The Mugging
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Where's Chandler? I want to wish him good luck on his first day.
錢德呢？ 我想要祝他第一天上班愉快
And I smelled bacon.
而且我也聞到培根香了
- He just left. - Who did?
-他才剛走 -誰才剛走？
Joey, you're never gonna believe it! She called!
喬伊，你不會相信的！她打來了！
- She did? - You got it!
-是嗎？ -你得到了！
- I did? - What is she talking about?
-是嗎？ -她是在說什麼呢？
I don't know, but it sounds great!
我不知道，但是聽起來倒是挺棒的！
Your agent called. You got that audition!
你的經紀人打電話來 你得到試演的機會了！
- With Leonard Hayes? - Yes!
-跟李奧海斯嗎？ -是的！
Oh, my God, that is great! It's for a play on Broadway.
我的天啊，太棒了！ 這是百老匯的一齣戲
And in a real theater. Not that little one underneath the deli like last time.
在一間真的劇院，而不是像上次一樣 是在快餐店下面的那種
- Is it a good play? - It must be.
-是一齣好戲嗎？ -肯定是的
I read it and didn't understand a single word!
因為我讀了劇本 而且根本連一個字都看不懂！
- Leonard Hayes is starring in it. - Yeah, and directing.
-李奧海斯也會參與演出 -是啊，兼導演
He was so good in that movie of Macbeth.
他在《馬克白》的演出真是精彩
- You saw that? - No, but I saw the previews.
-你有看嗎？ -沒有，但是我看了預告
They played it right before Jackass.
他們在《蠢蛋搞怪秀》播出之前有預告
- He's done some amazing work. - Oh, yeah.
-他做了些挺好的東西 -喔，是啊
I loved him in those phone commercials.
我喜歡他的電話廣告演出
When the monkey hits him in the face with the giant rubber phone..
猴子用巨形塑膠電話打他的臉
Maybe the monkey will be at the audition.
或許猴子也會在試演會上
Don't make me more nervous than I already am!
別讓我再更緊張了！
- Good morning. - Can I get you a cup of coffee, sir?
-早安 -我可以幫您倒咖啡嗎？先生
Oh, no, no. I'm an intern, just like you guys.
喔，不，我是實習生 就跟你們一樣
Except for the tie, the briefcase and the fact that I can rent a car.
除了這領帶，公事包，還有我已到達 合法年齡可以租車以外
Seriously, you're an intern?
真的？你是實習生？
I'm heading in a new career direction and you gotta start at the bottom.
我正在轉換職業跑道中 得要從基層做起
Dude.
老兄
I know I'm a little older than you guys, but it's not like I'm Bob Hope.
我知道我比你們大一些 但不至於像許不了一樣
The comedian. USO.
從前的一位喜劇演員，「小伯樂」
It's U.S.A., sir.
先生，是「老伯」了
This is Joey Tribbiani. Joey, these are the producers.
這位是喬伊崔比亞尼 喬伊，這幾位都是製作人
And as you probably already know, this is Leonard Hayes.
而你或許早就知道了 這位是李奧海斯
It is so amazing to meet you. I am such a big fan of your work.
能夠見到你真是太驚喜了 我是你的超級影迷
I've been blessed with a lot of great roles.
我很幸運能夠演出許多很棒的角色
Tell me about it, huh? "Unlimited nights and weekends!"
那倒是沒錯，「不限分鐘 不限時數！」
Are you making fun of me? Because I am not a sellout.
你是在取笑我嗎？ 我可是真的在為他們背書
I didn't do it for money. I believe in those phones!
我不是為錢而做的 我相信他們的電話好用！
I almost lost a cousin because of bad wireless service.
一家很爛的大哥大電話公司 害我差點失去一個表哥
No, I wasn't making fun of you. I think you were great in those commercials.
不，我不是在取笑你 我認為你在廣告裡的演出很棒
- Really? - Yeah.
-真的？ -是的
Well, I do bring a certain credibility to the role.
嗯，我倒是真的有說服力扮演那角色
Are you kidding? When they shoot you out of that cannon..
何止如此 當他們拍攝你從火箭筒衝出來時…
"Hang up that phone!"
「掛掉那個電話！」
- One take. - Wow.
-一次就拍成 -哇
- So shall we read? - Oh, yeah, sure.
-那我們要開始了嗎？ -喔，是的，當然
Top of Act 2. This is my entrance. You got it?
第二幕開始，我會出場，知道嗎？
What the hell are you still doing here?
你為什麼還愣在這裡？
- I think you know. - Bastard!
-我想你知道 -渾蛋！
I am what you made me. You know what? I could go right now.
這都是你造成的 你知道嗎？我現在就可以走
- Go! Go! - I can't.
-走！走！ -我不行
Oh, I want to, Long Pause..
喔，我想要，長暫停…
but I can't.
但是我不行
So sorry. You're not supposed to say "long pause."
很抱歉，但是你不應該說出「長暫停」
Oh! Oh, I thought that was your character's name. You know?
喔！喔，我以為那是你角色的名字
I thought you were, like, an Indian or something, you know, with the..
我以為你可能是印地安人 你知道的，名字都是…
No. Thank you so much for coming in. We appreciate it. Thank you.
不，謝謝你過來，我們很感激，謝謝
You don't want me to do it again?
你不要我再演一次嗎？
- I could do an accent. - No.
-我可以加上口音喔 -不用了
You know, Southern. "l could go right now, mon!" Huh?
你知道的，南方的口音 「我可以現在就走，老兄！」怎樣？
My God in heaven.
我的老天爺啊
Joey, hang on. Leonard, can we talk to you for a moment?
喬伊，等一下 李奧，我們可以跟你談一下嗎？
Yes? You've got to be kidding. He can't act.
怎樣？你是在開玩笑吧 他根本不會演戲
I don't care if you think he's hot.
我不在乎你是不是覺得他很帥
If you want to sleep with him, do it on your own time. This is a play.
如果你想要跟他上床，隨你便 但是這是一場戲劇表演
If you insist on this..
如果你堅持這樣…
I will call my agent so fast..
我會馬上打電話給我的經紀人
on a cell phone connection so clear, he's gonna think I'm next door!
用話質清晰的大哥大打 讓他以為我人就在隔壁！
Hi, thank you so much for whispering for my benefit.
嗨，謝謝你這麼小聲幫我說話
Tell me what I did wrong. I'd love to work on it and try it again for you.
跟我說我是哪裡不好 我會改進，然後再表演一次給你看
And also, how you doing?
還有，你好嗎？
Give me another chance. I really want to get better. Please?
再給我一次機會 我真的想要改進，拜託
If you want to come back today..
如果你想要明天再回來
- here are my notes. Ready? - Yeah.
-這是我的建議，準備好了嗎？ -好了
- You're in your head. Thinking too much. - I really doubt that.
-你在你的腦子裡，想太多了 -我真的很懷疑
No, no. It's that you're not connected with anything in your body.
不是，你並沒有跟你的身體做連結
There's no urgency. The scene is a struggle.
沒表達出迫切感，這一幕是很掙扎的
It's a race. Also, what you did was horizontal.
是一種競賽，還有 你的表演是水平的
Don't be afraid to explore the vertical.
別害怕發掘垂直的情感
And don't learn the words. Let the words learn you.
而且不要體會那些文字 讓文字體會你
Couldn't I just sleep with the producer?
我不能跟製作人睡一睡就好了嗎？
我快不行了，快爆炸了
Hey, do you want to go to dinner tonight?
嘿，要不要一起去吃晚餐？
I can't. I've got a date with that waitress, Katie.
不行，我要跟那個女服務生凱蒂約會
I know we've only gone out, like, twice, but I don't know..
我們只有出去過好像兩次 但是我不知道…
- I have a good feeling about her. - Oh, I hear divorce bells.
-我對她的印象很不錯 -喔，我聽到離婚的聲音了
Give me your wallets, and there won't be a problem.
錢包給我，不然你們就慘了
- What? - I have a gun.
-什麼？ -我有槍
Okay, relax, Phoebe. Just stay calm.
好的，不要怕，菲比 冷靜一點
Oh, my God, I can't find my wallet!
我的天，我找不到皮夾子！
- All right, lady, now give me your purse. - No.
-好了，女士，該你把皮包給我了 -不要
What do you mean "no"? I knew you'd be my death, Phoebe Buffay!
「不要」？你是什麼意思？我就知道 我會死在你手上，菲比布菲！
- Lowell, is that you? - Phoebe?
-羅威，是你嗎？ -菲比？
- Oh, my God! - Unbelievable! Oh, my God!
-喔，我的天啊！ -真不敢相信，我的天啊！
I'm sorry. Ross, this is my old friend, Lowell, from the streets!
我很抱歉，羅斯， 這是我街頭的老朋友，羅威
- Lowell, Ross. - Ross, nice to meet you.
-羅威，這位是羅斯 -羅斯，很高興認識你
Yeah, a real pleasure.
是啊，真是高興
It's been so long! Oh, so long.
真是好久了，哇，真久
- I can't believe you're still doing this. - I know. But I quit smoking.
-不敢相信你還在幹這行 -我知道，但是我戒煙了
Good for you.
好極了
You look like you're doing well.
你看起來好像過得不錯
I guess your mugging days are behind you.
我猜搶劫的日子對你而言 已經是過去式了
Oh, my God. Phoebe, you used to mug people?
我的天，菲比 你以前會搶劫人？
Excuse me, Ross, old friends catching up.
對不起，羅斯 我們老朋友正在敘舊耶
- How'd the audition go? - They want to see me again, but..
-試演進行得如何呢？ -他們要我再去，但是…
Leonard Hayes did not like me.
李奧海斯並不喜歡我
- What happened? - He said I wasn't urgent enough.
-怎麼了？ -他說我迫切感不夠
Everything I did was horizontal, and I should be more vertical.
我演的是水平的 應該要垂直一點
- He said that I should think less. - Well, so far so good.
-他說我應該不要想太多 -喔，目前為止還不錯啊
Honey, I'm old!
親愛的，我老了！
I didn't know you were coming home for lunch.
我不知道你要回家吃中飯
- Can I get you anything? - Sure, a tube of Polident?
-想要來點什麼嗎？ -當然囉，假牙清潔劑…
Some Depends?
包大人紙尿布
Birthday wishes from Willard Scott.
白光唱的生日快樂歌
What's wrong?
怎麼了？
I am so much older than these other interns. I can't compete with them.
我比其他的實習生老太多了 我無法跟他們競爭
So you're a little older.
你是年紀比較大一點沒錯
Look at the positive. You have all this life experience.
往好處想，你有更多的生活經歷
Yes, but I don't think life experience is gonna help me with these.
是的，但是我不認為生活經歷 可以幫助我這個
Wow! It's like they're on fire!
哇！它們就像著火了！
- What are they? - Prototype sneakers.
-這些是什麼？ -樣品鞋
I need ideas on how to sell them. Which I can't do..
我需要想出該怎麼賣 而我辦不到
because no self-respecting adult would ever wear these.
因為有自尊的成人不會穿這種東西的
I'll give you $500 for them.
我給你五百塊買下這雙
- What am I supposed to do? - Come on, sneakers are easy.
-我應該怎麼辦呢？ -別這樣，步鞋很容易啦！
- You wear them all the time. - They're not called sneakers anymore.
-你也常常在穿啊 -它們現在不叫做步鞋了
They're called "kicks" or "skids." I think I heard somebody say "slorps."
改叫「溜鞋」或是「滑輪鞋」 我還聽到有人說「輪鞋」
They've got wheels that pop out from the bottom so you can roll around..
它們底部有輪子突出來 讓你可以滑來滑去
because apparently walking is too much exercise.
因為很顯然，走路太耗費體力了
"Kids! Kids! Roll your way to childhood obesity!"
「孩子們！孩子們！ 向前滑到兒童肥胖區吧！」
Kids today have such an easier time getting fat.
這年頭小孩子要變胖可真快啊！
Would you help me try to sell these?
你可以幫我賣這些東西嗎？
Okay. Have you considered using a girl with huge knockers?
好的，有沒有想過用大波霸呢？
That's not what they're looking for.
那不會是他們想要的
Hey, that would work on me.
嘿，那對我很有用喔
Why do you think I buy Mrs. Butterworth's?
你想我為什麼要買津津蘆筍汁呢？
（中央咖啡廳）
You'll never guess what just happened.
你不會相信剛剛發生什麼事
- Phoebe and I got mugged! - Are you okay?
-菲比跟我被搶了 -你們沒事吧
Yeah. Phoebe knew the mugger.
沒事，因為菲比認識那個搶匪
How do you know a mugger?
你怎麼會認識搶匪呢？
I'm sorry, I have friends outside the six of us.
不好意思，除了我們六個人之外 我還是有其他朋友的
Know how she knew him? Because Phoebe used to mug people.
你知道他們是怎麼認識的嗎？ 因為菲比以前也是在搶劫別人
Seriously?
真的嗎？
Well, I'm not proud of it, but, you know..
我不覺得很光榮，但是你們知道的
when I was living on the street and I needed money for food and stuff..
當我流落街頭的時候 我也需要錢買食物之類的東西
- That is awful. - I wasn't rich like you guys, okay?
-真是太糟糕了 -我不像你們那麼有錢，好嗎？
I didn't eat gold and have a flying pony.
我沒有金湯匙也沒有飛天馬
I had a hard life. My mother was killed by a drug dealer.
我的生活很苦 我媽被毒販給殺了
- Your mother killed herself. - She was a drug dealer.
-你媽是自殺的 -她自己就是毒販
It was a good thing she knew him. I was about to do some serious damage.
幸好菲比認識他 否則我會讓他死得很難看
Okay.
好吧
This must have brought back some bad memories for you, Ross.
這一定讓你想起不好的回憶，羅斯
- Why? - Ross was mugged as a kid.
-為什麼？ -羅斯小時候被搶過
- You were? - Yeah. And it was pretty traumatic.
-是嗎？ -是的，受到非常嚴重的創傷
It was outside St. Mark's Comics.
就在漫畫王外面
I was minding my business, seeing what kind of trouble Spider-Man was into.
我正在做我自己的事 看蜘蛛人又惹上什麼麻煩了
Wonder Woman.
是神力女超人
Anyway, I was heading towards this bakery..
反正，我正在要去麵包店的路上
to pick up a couple of dozen linzer tortes for someone..
幫某人買幾個蛋糕
when out of nowhere, this thug with a pipe jumps out and says:
然後不知道從哪裡冒出來的惡棍 拿著一條管子跳出來說…
- "Give me your money, punk!" - Oh, my God.
-「小子！錢交出來」 -喔，我的天啊
I know. And the worst part was, they took my backpack..
我知道，最糟糕的是 他們搶走了我的背包
which had all the original artwork I did for my own comic book, Science Boy.
裡面有我自己畫的漫畫，《科學小子》
Oh, yeah! What was his super power again?
對啊，他的超能力是什麼？
A super-human thirst for knowledge.
一個渴望知識的超人
I better get to class.
我要趕去上課了
Are there any more of your friends I should look out for?
你還有其他朋友我需要小心的嗎，菲比？
No. Actually, you might want to stay away from Jane Street.
沒有，事實上 你或許得離詹恩街遠點
That's where Stabby Joe works.
那是刺客喬的地盤
- I think we have a problem here. - What?
-我想我們有麻煩了 -怎麼了？
Back in my mugging days, I worked St. Mark's Comics.
在我當搶匪的時候 漫畫王是我的地盤
- Yeah? - A pipe was my weapon of choice..
-是嗎？ -我用的武器是管子
and preteen, comic-book nerds were my meat.
而且小孩子、漫畫書蟲 都是我的目標
So?
所以呢？
There was one kid who had a sticker on his backpack that said:
有一個小孩子 在背包上有張貼紙寫著…
- "Geology rocks!" - "Geology rocks!"
-「地質學酷斃了！」 -「地質學酷斃了！」
- Oh, my God! - I know! I mugged Ross!
-喔，我的天啊！ -我知道！我搶了羅斯！
- You're late. - I know. I'm sorry.
-你遲到了 -我知道，我很抱歉
But can I just run to the bathroom?
但是我可以先去上廁所嗎？
- No. Leonard doesn't wait. - But I am bursting with Yoo-hoo!
-不行，李奧是不等人的 -但是我快尿出來了！
Joey, here we go! Let's go. Very quickly.
喬伊，來吧！ 我們開始，快一點
- I really need.. - We must go now, quickly.
-我真的想要… -我們現在就得開始，快點
- Yeah. Yes, sir. - Ready?
-好，是的 -好了嗎？
- What the hell are you still doing here? - I think you know!
-你還在這裡做什麼呢？ -我想你知道
- Oh, you sick bastard! - I am what you made me! Know what?
-喔，你該死的渾蛋！ -這都是你造成的，你知道嗎？
- What? - I could go right now.
-什麼？ -我可以現在就走
- Then go. Go! - Oh, I can't. I want to, but I can't!
-那就走，走啊！ -喔，我不行，我很想，但是我不行！
Cut. That was good!
停，演得好！
- Very good. You did everything I asked. - I did?
-非常精采，你做到我的要求了 -是嗎？
Yes. Plus which, you've got this, I don't know, this squirmy quality..
是的，而且你把這種... 扭曲的特質...
you bring to the character I couldn't have imagined.
加入到這個角色中 我想都沒想過
Here's what we're gonna do:
我們接下來可以這樣…
Come back tomorrow for the final callbacks.
明天過來參加最後的試演
Do all of this, what you got going now. But you know what?
照你今天演的，但是你知道嗎？
More. More. Can you do that?
加強，再加強，你可以嗎？
Sure. I don't have time to say thank you because I really gotta go!
當然，我沒有時間說謝了 我真的得走了！
Look at that! Still in character. I like him.
瞧瞧他！還那麼入戲，我喜歡他
I plant seeds. I can't explain it. I don't know.
我播了種，快得無法解釋 我不知道
- Hey. What are you doing? - Putting on the sneakers..
-嘿，你在做什麼？ -在試穿步鞋
to get in the young mindset, see if it sparks anything.
融入年輕人的世界 看會不會激發出什麼點子
- Oh, anything yet? - Yes, how's this?
-喔，想出什麼了嗎？ -是的，聽聽看這個
"They're so uncomfortable, it's like getting kicked in the nuts for your feet."
「它們舒服到就像是 被腳踢到蛋蛋一樣」
-Hi! -Hi!
-嘿！ -嘿！
You're probably wondering what I'm doing.
你可能很納悶，不知道我在做什麼
No, that seems about right.
不，看起來很正常
Yesterday at my audition, I had to pee. Apparently, that makes me a good actor.
昨天在試演的時候我好想尿尿 很明顯地，那讓我演的很棒
I got a callback, so I'm drinking everything. Oh, by the way..
可以參加最後試演 所以我要喝多一點東西，對了
that eggnog in our fridge was great!
我們冰箱裡面的蛋奶實在太好喝了
- Joey, that was formula. - We gotta get more of that.
-喬伊，那是特調嬰兒奶粉 -我們一定要多買一些
These aren't half bad. You should suggest these to Ralph Lauren.
這些東西挺不錯的 你應該要向洛夫羅倫推薦
Okay, first of all, that's stupid. Second, I'm not allowed to talk to Ralph.
好的，第一，那很蠢 再來，他們不允許我跟洛夫說話
All right. I feel younger already.
好的，我已經開始覺得年輕多了
Yeah, I think I broke my hip.
我想我摔傷臀部了
- Hey, you! - Hey.
-嘿，你來了 -嘿
Hey. How was class?
嘿，課上得怎樣？
No one asks me that. What's wrong?
沒有人這樣問過我，怎麼了？
- Nothing. I really want to know. - Oh.
-沒事，我真的想知道而已 -喔
Well, there was actually a rather lively discussion about the Pleistocene..
我們針對更新世 有很熱烈的討論
All right, nothing is worth this.
好了，我不需要這樣折磨自己
I have a confession to make.
我有件事需要對你坦白
Okay, you know that girl that mugged you when you were a kid?
你記得那個在你小時候 搶劫過你的女生嗎？
What are you talking about? It wasn't a girl. It was this huge dude.
你在說什麼呢？那不是女生 是個高壯的男生
He had a pitchfork and a sword.
他帶著草耙，還有一把劍
You don't have to lie anymore. I know that it was a 14-year-old girl.
你不需要說謊了 我知道是個十四歲女生
- No, it wasn't. - Yes, it was.
-不，不是 -是，是的
You don't think I would have defended myself against a 14-year-old..?
你認為我不會反抗 一個十四歲女生嗎？
- "Give me your money, punk!" - Oh, my God, it was you!
-「小子！錢交出來」 -我的天，那是你！
I can't believe it. You mugged me?
我真不敢相信，你搶劫我
Yeah. And I'm so, so sorry, Ross. I'm sorry.
是的，而且我很抱歉，羅斯 我很抱歉
But, you know, if you think about it, it's kind of neat.
但是如果你仔細想想，這倒是有點酷
I mean, well, it's just that I've always felt kind of like an outsider.
我是說，我常常覺得我像是個局外人
You know, the rest of you have connections that go way back..
你們其他的人都彼此認識很久了
and, you know, now you and I have a great one.
而現在，你跟我也有老交情了
It's not the best!
這並不是好事！
I know. Please forgive me. I don't know what to say.
我知道，請原諒我，我不知道該說什麼
There's nothing you can say! That was the most humiliating thing ever.
你不用說什麼！那是我這輩子 最可恥的事了
- Even more humiliating than.. - Let's not do this!
-甚至比… -我們不要說了！
And then, at the end of the commercial, the girls get out of the hot tub..
然後在廣告結尾，女孩子們離開浴池
and start making out with each other.
開始一起親熱
That's interesting.
有趣
Just one thought: You didn't mention the shoes.
順便提一下，你沒有提到鞋子
Who's next? Chandler.
下一個是誰？錢德
You start with a guy putting on the shoes.
一開始有個男的穿上這鞋
- He's about my age. - Your age?
-他大約是我的年紀 -你的年紀？
He's rolling down the street and he starts to lose control.
他在街上滑行著，接著就失去控制
Maybe he falls. Maybe he hurts himself.
或許他跌倒了，或者受傷了
Just then, a kid comes flying by wearing the shoes.
就在這時候，有個小孩 穿著這雙鞋飛過去
He jumps over the old guy and laughs. And the line reads:
他跳過那個老男人，然後大笑 接著廣告詞出現…
"Not suitable for adults."
「成人不宜」
- Well, Chandler, that's great. - Thank you, sir.
-錢德，這個很棒 -謝謝你，先生
Or, man who's two years younger than me.
或是，比我小兩歲的人
You see, that has a clear selling point. It appeals to our key demographic.
你們瞧，銷售訊息很清楚 抓住了我們主要客戶群的心態
- How did you come up with that? - I don't know! I don't know!
-你是怎麼想出來的呢？ -我不知道！我不知道！
I was just trying to get into a young mindset, and stuff started to flow.
我只是設法用年輕的心態去思考 然後點子就出現了
- That is great. Good work. - Thank you.
-太棒了，做得好 -謝謝
We'll see all of you tomorrow.
那我們大家明天見
The cold weather hurts my hip.
冷天讓我的臀部很痛
Hey, Ross. I know you're still mad at me, but can I just talk to you for a sec?
嘿，羅斯，我知道你還在生我的氣 但是我可以跟你談一下嗎？
Sure, go ahead. Oh, sorry. Sure, go ahead.
當然，說吧，喔，等等 當然，說吧
I just really wanted to apologize again.
我真的想要再次跟你道歉
And also show you something I think you'll find very exciting.
而且讓你看些 你會覺得很興奮的東西
（街上的垃圾）
Oh, my God! "Crap from the street!"
喔，我的天啊！「街上的垃圾！」
Look, Ross. In this box..
聽著，羅斯，在這箱子裡
are all the things I got from mugging that I thought were too special to sell..
都是在搶來的東西之中 我覺得太特別，而不想賣掉…
or smoke.
或是燒掉的東西
Anyway, I was looking through it, and I found..
反正，我在整理時發現了…
Science Boy.
《科學小子》
Oh, my God!
喔，我的天啊！
I never thought I'd see this again.
我從沒想過我會再見到它
It's all here!
全部都在裡面
What made you save it all these years?
你為什麼這些年都留著它呢？
I guess I just thought it was really good.
我猜我只是覺得它很棒
And maybe it would be worth something one day.
而且或許有一天會很值錢
You really thought Science Boy was worth saving?
你真的認為《科學小子》值得收藏？
Yeah. But you should know I also have a jar of Vaseline and a cat skull in here.
是的，但是你應該知道 我還留了一罐凡士林跟一副貓骨頭
Still, this is amazing!
不管，這還是很令人驚喜！
Oh, my God. Thank you, Phoebe.
我的天，謝謝你，菲比
You're welcome. Thank you for Science Boy. I learned a lot from him.
不用客氣，謝謝你的科學小子 我從他身上學到很多
You're welcome.
不用客氣
Wait a minute. Did you add something to him?
等等，你有加東西到他身上嗎？
Oh, yeah.
喔，是啊
You see, the way you drew him..
你瞧你畫他的樣子
there was no way he was ever gonna get Gravity Girl.
他是不可能會把到地心引力女孩的
He looked like a Ken doll in those tights.
他看起來像穿了緊身褲的肯尼
What's that? What are you..?
那是什麼？你是在…
"Is that a beaker or are you happy to see me?"
「那是個大杯子，還是 你很高興見到我呢？」
I don't get it.
我不明白
- I need an answer! - I can't tell you something I don't know.
-我需要答案！ -我無法告訴你我不知道的事
- You know! - I don't know!
-你知道的！ -我不知道！
- I need an answer now! - You want an answer? The answer is..
-我現在就要答案！ -你要答案嗎？答案就是…
She never loved me. She only loved you.
她從未愛過我，她只愛你
You knew this all along and you never told me?
你一直都知道而你卻沒有告訴我？
I can never forgive you, or myself. I have nothing to live for. Bang! And scene!
我永遠都不會原諒你，或是我自己 我沒有活下去的必要了，結束！
Absolutely amazing.
精采得不得了
- The part is yours. - Thanks! Now I really gotta go.
-這個角色是你的了 -謝謝！現在我得要走了
No, wait! Congratulations! You did it.
不，等等！恭喜了！你辦到了
You did it. You can relax now. Yeah.
你辦到了，現在可以放輕鬆了，是的
Wow! That's a big cable bill.
哇！第四台帳單真貴
You don't have a job, but you have no problem ordering porn.
你沒有工作 可是倒很敢付錢看色情片啊
On a Saturday afternoon?
在星期六下午？
I was in the house!
我也在家耶！
Hey. Phoebe didn't by any chance mention that..
嘿，菲比有沒有提到…
She was the huge guy that mugged you? Yeah.
她就是那個搶了你的大塊頭嗎？有
I see. You didn't happen to tell..
我知道了，你有沒有告訴…
- Everybody we know? Yeah. - Great. Thanks.
-我們認識的每個人嗎？我有 -太好了，謝謝